Nick Mosher

2723 Maverick Lane, Lawrence KS 66046 **Phone**: 785-813-1246

E-mail: nick@mosher.me
Website: http://nick.mosher.me



Hello:

My name is Nick Mosher and I am the customer experience manager for a local bank in the Kansas City area. I bring a combination of Project Management and Interaction Design skills to my job and in the future I would like to apply my diverse and unique skill set to the private space industry.

I have an innovative work style and I draw from my interdisciplinary experiences to design, develop and manage projects. I have designed lighting and sound for theatre productions, created and hosted Web sites for clients and lead complex online banking upgrades smoothly and efficiently.

My experience in workflow and process management enables me to stay agile in the ever-changing local banking market, managing and guiding projects efficiently to completion. For example, I managed a project to develop an online toolkit allowing customers to switch banks online. To complete the project, I employed a completely iterative process that minimized scope creep, allowing my team and me to complete the product under an aggressive timeline on a meager budget.

I am attending the New Space conference both to learn what space companies could currently use my unique skills and to discover what further training or experience would benefit me as I seek employment in the private space industry. I am a quick and eager learner and would love to find fulfilling employment working to further space exploration.

I look forward to hearing from you.

Sincerely,

Nick Mosher

Nick Mosher

2723 Maverick Lane, Lawrence KS 66046 **Phone**: 785-813-1246

E-mail: nick@mosher.me
Website: http://nick.mosher.me



Executive Summary

I would like to use my wide range of skills and experience in project management and design in order to enter the private space industry. My project management techniques have been agile to best combat the ever-changing dynamics of the local banking market.

Education

University of Kansas - Design, BFA (2005)

- Designed stage lighting and sound for 10+ shows in 4 years
- Awarded several technical theater awards and scholarships

Experience

MosherDesign (www.mosherdesign.com)

Freelance Designer (2005 – Present)

- Designed, developed and launched http://blairsfostersocks.org, a site to accept donations in response to a local tragedy, in one day. So far, we have collected over \$4,500 in small donations.
- Wrote the "gold-standard" of all online banking comparison matrices.
- Interaction design, Web site design and graphic design.
- Sound and lighting design for various shows.

Eternal Second Designs (www.eternalsecond.com)

Co-Owner, Founding Partner (2005 – Present)

- Partnered with Bill Parrott (http://chimericdream.com) to create a local Web design firm.
- Designed and launch 12+ Web sites in close collaboration with our clients.

First Olathe Bancshares (2007 - Present)

430 E Santa Fe, Olathe, KS 66061

Customer Experience Manager

- Lead Project Management Office.
- Lead Innovation Team.
- Developed and Lead Fraud Communications Team.
- Managed Web and marketing projects as well as online banking implementation and upgrades.
- Designed all Web and online related marketing, communications and educational programs.
- Identified and solved gaps in customer experience.
- Lead development of social media education campaigns to internal staff.

- Research and development of modern online marketing and communication including, but not limited to, social media.
- Designed and managed implementation of a revolutionary <u>switch kit Web application</u>.

Technology Project Coordinator

- Wrote and published 150 page comprehensive online banking user's guide.
- **)** Co-lead focus groups related to Web site redesigns and perspectives on banking.
- Saved the bank over \$20,000 a year by self-hosting of microsite solutions.
- Saved the bank over \$28,500 a year by leading a single campaign to switch customers to electronic statements.
- Developed <u>Bank Owned Real-Estate websites</u> for two banks
- Managed Web and marketing projects for three banks
- Managed online banking implementation and upgrades for three banks
- Designed many Web and online related marketing, communications and educational programs.

Technology Assistant

- Coordinated services with online banking vendors.
- Provided key assistance in implementing major online banking service conversion.
- Maintained and managed online banking services for customers and bank officials.
- Assisted <u>major website conversion</u>, implementations and upgrades across two banks.
- Supported customers directly during times of extremely high call volume.
- Co-Founded Innovation Team for anybody at the bank to make innovative recommendations on internal processes, products and marketing plans.

Skills and Related

- Agile Project Management
- ▶ HTML, CSS, PHP Rapid Development
- Web and Graphic Design
- Interaction and Usability Design
- Sandler Sales System Trained
- Microsoft SharePoint Services 2007 Trained and Certified
- Vendor Management
- Understanding Complex Banking Systems
- Marketing and Brand Management
- Managing Professional Social Media
- Workflow and Productivity Systems Adept (Based on GTD System)
- Notary Public
- Eagle Scout

LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/in/mosherdesign

Twitter: http://twitter.com/moshner
Personal Blog: http://nickandemily.us
Porfolio: http://www.mosherdesign.com